<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<text>
	<heading>MAZOIN</heading>
	<body>
		<page1>
Agreement to Terms
Please read the following important terms and conditions before you download the Mazoin app. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under the age of 18 you are agreeing to these Terms on behalf of yourself and your children who are authorised to use the Mazoin App pursuant to these Terms. By downloading the Mazoin App you agree to these terms. If you do not agree to these terms, do not download the Mazoin App. 
We take our responsibilities as a provider of online and app-based games seriously and follow the Principles for online and app-based games (Principles) published by the Competition and Markets Authority (CMA). This means that, in particular, we will:
give you clear and accurate information on costs, the game and on us;
make it clear where there is an in-game promotion of paid-for content or promotion of any other product or service;
make sure that paid-for and non-paid-for options are presented clearly and given equal prominence;
not exploit or pressurise any game-players who are children to make a purchase or persuade others to make purchases for them; and
only take payments from you with your knowledge and express authorisation.
The information in this summary box summarises our main responsibilities under the Principles. It is not intended to replace the contract below which you should read carefully.
</page1>
<page2>
This contract sets out:
your legal rights and responsibilities;
our legal rights and responsibilities; 
how our Tournaments will run; and
certain key information required by law.
In this contract:
‘We’, ‘us’ or ‘our’ means Forward Gaming Limited; and
‘You’ or ‘your’ means, you, the person using the app under licence.
If you don’t understand any of this contract, or would like it in another format, please contact us at contact@mazoin.com
Who are we?
Forward Gaming Limited is a company registered in England and Wales under company number: 10265862.
Our registered office is at: Lyndon House Rmy, 62 Hagley Road, Edgbaston, Birmingham, England, B16 8PE.
Our VAT number is: [insert details].
</page2>
<page3>
Agreement
If you download the Mazoin App you agree to be legally bound by this contract. When you click on the ‘download’ button (or similar) a legally binding contract will be in place between you and us. 
By downloading the Mazoin App you also agree to be legally bound by:
our Privacy Policy [insert hyperlink];  
our Cookie Policy [insert hyperlink],
and these documents form part of this contract as though set out in full here. We will also issue rules of play from time to time.  
The Apple App Store, Google Play, and Windows Phone Store terms (as applicable)  may also apply and may contain rules and policies about how you can use the Mazoin App. The Apple App Store, Google Play, or Windows Phone Store (as applicable) rules and policies will apply instead of these terms where there are differences between the two. 
This contract is only available in English. No other languages will apply to this contract.
You have no right to cancel this contract once the automatic downloading of the Mazoin App starts. You understand and acknowledge that by downloading the Mazoin App you lose your right of withdrawal from the contract. If you no longer accept these terms you must cease using the Mazoin App and remove it from your device. 
Operating System Requirements
The Mazoin App requires the following operating system requirements:
Device
Version
Memory
iOS
[8.0 or later]
Minimum [•]
Android
[4.4 or later]
Minimum [•]
Windows
[7 or later]
Minimum [•]
We recommend that you ensure that you download the latest version of whatever operating system you use to ensure that you have the optimum Mazoin experience. 
Compatibility is not guaranteed for all devices. The Mazoin App may not run on certain devices even if they have compatible operating systems versions installed. 
An internet connection is required to take part in a Tournament although certain gameplay features will also be available offline. You will also need an internet connection to submit your results. 
We cannot be responsible if the Mazoin App does not operate properly due to your system. If you experience issues, please update your software.   
Support for the Mazoin App
If you want to learn more about the App or have any problems using it, please contact us at contact@mazoin.com
Use of the Mazoin App
In return for your agreeing to comply with these terms you may:
download a copy of the Mazoin App onto your device and view, use and display the Mazoin App on such device for your personal use only; 
receive and use any free supplementary software code or update of the Mazoin App incorporating 'patches' and corrections of errors as we may provide to you. 
You will not own the Mazoin App but will have our permission to use it; this is known as a licence. The licence is personal to you. You can use it wherever you want in the world but only if you comply with local laws. 
Licence Restrictions
You agree that you will:
not rent, lease, sub-license, loan, provide, or otherwise make available, the Mazoin App in any form, in whole or in part to any person without prior written consent from us;
not copy the Mazoin App, except as part of the normal use of the Mazoin App or where it is necessary for the purpose of back-up or operational security;
not translate, merge, adapt, vary, alter or modify, the whole or any part of the Mazoin App, nor permit the Mazoin App or any part of it to be combined with, or become incorporated in, any other programs, except as necessary to use the Mazoin App on devices as permitted in these terms;
not disassemble, de-compile, reverse engineer or create derivative works based on the whole or any part of the Mazoin App nor attempt to do any such things.
Acceptable Use Restrictions
You must: 
not use the Mazoin App in any unlawful manner, for any unlawful purpose, or in any manner inconsistent with these terms, or act fraudulently or maliciously, for example, by hacking into or inserting malicious code, such as viruses, or harmful data, into the Mazoin App or any operating system;
not infringe our intellectual property rights or those of any third party in relation to your use of the Mazoin App; 
not transmit any material that is defamatory, offensive or otherwise objectionable in relation to your use of the Mazoin App; 
not use the Mazoin App in a way that could damage, disable, overburden, impair or compromise our systems or security or interfere with other users; and
not collect or harvest any information or data from our systems or attempt to decipher any transmissions to or from the servers running.
Intellectual Property Rights
All intellectual property rights in the Mazoin App throughout the world belong to us (or our licensors) and the rights in the Mazoin App are licensed (not sold) to you. You have no intellectual property rights in, or to, the Mazoin App other than the right to use them in accordance with these terms.
Changes to these terms
We may need to change these terms to reflect changes in law or best practice, or to deal with additional features which we introduce. 
We will give you notice of any change when you next start the Mazoin App or through other communications. Please review the updated terms; if you continue to use the Mazoin App after we have posted modified terms on our Mazoin App, or otherwise communicated them to you, you are indicating to us that you agree to be bound by the updated terms. If you do not accept the notified changes you may continue to use the Mazoin App in accordance with the existing terms but certain new features may not be available to you. 
We may change or discontinue all or part of the Mazoin App at any time without notice. 
Updates to the Mazoin App
From time to time we may automatically update the Mazoin App to improve performance, enhance functionality, reflect changes to the operating system or address security issues and you may need to update the Mazoin App for these reasons. Additionally, each new Tournament will require an update. You will need to download the update if you wish to take part in a Tournament.  If you choose not to install such updates or if you opt out of automatic updates you may not be able to continue to use the Mazoin App. 
</page3>
<page4>
Eligibility 
You will not be able to use the Mazoin App if:
the digital content is unavailable;
you are not allowed to buy the Mazoin App from us or we are not allowed to sell the Mazoin App to you.
You must be 18 or over to accept these terms. If you are younger than 18, you can only download and play the Mazoin App, if your parent(s) or legal guardian have/has reviewed these terms and allowed you to download the Mazoin App. We may require adequate proof of your identity and age and consent from a parent or guardian at any time. 
We may, in our sole discretion, refuse access to the Mazoin App to any person if we determine that you have violated any of these terms and conditions. We may change the eligibility criteria at any time. 
If you downloaded the Mazoin App onto any phone or other device not owned by you, you must have the owner’s permission to do so. You will be responsible for complying with these terms, whether or not you own the phone or other device. 
Please note, there is separate eligibility criteria that applies if you take part in a Tournament.
Availability
We do not guarantee that the Mazoin App, or any content on it, will always be available or be uninterrupted. Access to the Mazoin App is permitted on a temporary basis. We may suspend, withdraw, discontinue or change all or any part of the Mazoin App without notice. We will not deliberately remove the Mazoin App to prevent the completion of a Tournament, but we will not be liable to you if the Mazoin App is unavailable at any time or for any period. 
Where is it available?
The Mazoin App is available to use by people residing in the United Kingdom. We do not represent that the content available on or through the Mazoin App is appropriate or available in other locations. We may limit the availability of the Mazoin App to any person or geographic area at any time. If you choose to access the Mazoin App from outside the United Kingdom, you do so at your own risk, and must ensure that you comply with local laws.  You must have a UK residential address in order to meet our eligibility criteria for a Tournament (see below for eligibility). 
Account Registration
To use the Mazoin App you will need to create an account (your Account). You can login to your Account through your pre-existing account Facebook account, or directly through the Mazoin App. Where you login through Facebook we will create your Account by extracting certain personal information (such as your email address) that you privacy settings on your Facebook account permit us to access. You will need to upload a photograph of you to your Account. 
If you choose, or you are provided with, a user identification code, password or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential. You must not disclose it to any third party. We have the right to disable any user identification code or password, whether chosen by you or allocated by us, at any time, if in our reasonable opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these terms.
If you know or suspect that anyone other than you knows your user identification code or password, please notify us promptly at contact@mazoin.com.
You will need to provide a valid email address if you wish to take part in a Tournament. This is so we can contact you if you win a prize. 
Accurate Information
Please ensure you provide us with accurate, complete, and up-to-date information. You agree to update such information as needed and understand that we cannot be held liable if you fail to keep your information complete, accurate and up-to-date. 
We may collect technical data about your device
By using the Mazoin App you agree to us collecting and using technical information about the devices you use the Mazoin App on to improve and provide our products to you. 
The Mazoin App may use location data sent from your device. You can turn off this functionality at any time by turning off the location services settings for the Mazoin App on your device. If you use the Mazoin App, you consent to our transmission, collection, retention, maintenance, processing and use of your location data to provide and improve location-based functions of the Mazoin App.   
Playing Mazoin
Once you have downloaded the Mazoin App and registered and logged-in to your Account, you can play Mazoin. 
Full information about gameplay features, functionality and competitions can be found within the Mazoin App.
Mazoin is free but you may purchase virtual items (such as additional zoins) inside the Mazoin App to progress in the game by spending real money (Virtual Extras). The cost for the Virtual Extras will include any applicable tax. Means of payment may vary depending upon which app store or platform you are using.  
Virtual Extras cannot be exchanged into real money or refunded. You understand that you do not own the Virtual Extras, but have a licence to use the Virtual Extras within the Mazoin App. Any Virtual Extras not used during a Tournament, will roll over to the following month’s game. However, you will not receive money or other compensation for unused Virtual Extras if your Account is closed. This provision is not intended to limit your cancellation rights under the Consumer Rights Act 2015. 
We may, in our sole discretion, provide opportunities for you to purchase Virtual Extras at discounted rates. You may only purchase such Virtual Extras at the times permitted by us, and we do not imply or warrant that the same discount will be available at any or all times. 
All payments will be made through the applicable app store that you use. 
Mazoin Tournament
Each month, a new Tournament will begin. You can take part in the Tournament through your Account on the App. You may need to download the appropriate update each month if your device is not set to receive automatic updates. The specific Tournament rules that will apply to each Tournament can be found within the Mazoin App. 
The Mazoin App will contain a countdown which will let you know when the Tournament will start, and for how long it will last. 
Cash prizes will be available at different stages of the Tournament upon the achievement of the stated highscores (as set out in each particular Tournament’s rules) and are on a first-past-the-post basis. This will be determined by the time that your device uploads your scores to us. If you have completed the level offline, your time will not count until your progress has been submitted. We recommend that you permit your device to make and receive automatic updates so as to ensure your score is submitted at the right time.  
At the end of the Tournament, whomever has achieved the highest score will be eligible to win the Tournament prize of £10,000. Your score must be submitted before the end of the tournament to qualify. If more than one person achieves the same highest score, the £10,000 prize fund will be split equally among those eligible players. 
To be eligible to win the prize, the user must meet the following eligibility criteria:
all contenders must be [14] or over;
all contenders must have a valid UK residential address and a valid email address, 
and We reserve the right to verify and require evidence of each of the above elements before any prize will be issued. 
In addition, each contender must submit a photograph to their Account and agree to our reasonable use of your photograph for the purposes of promotion and verification of the Tournament.  We may also ask you to attend promotional events. Your photograph will only be used in this context and in accordance with all applicable data protection laws. 
If you have qualified for a prize, we will contact you to confirm your full details and eligibility for the prize fund. The prize will be presented to you within [30 days] of confirmation of eligibility.
If we suspect that you have cheated or have hacked (or attempted to cheat or hack, or otherwise fraudulent tried to submit a score that you have not achieved) we reserve the right to withhold any prize monies until such time as we have been able to make full investigations. Prizes will only be presented when we are satisfied that you have properly achieved your score.  
Our Responsibility for Loss or Damage Suffered By You
We are responsible to you for foreseeable loss and damage caused by us If we fail to comply with these terms, we are responsible for loss or damage you suffer that is a foreseeable result of our breaking these terms or our failing to use reasonable care and skill, but we are not responsible for any loss or damage that is not foreseeable. Loss or damage is foreseeable if either it is obvious that it will happen or if, at the time you accepted these terms, both we and you knew it might happen.
We do not exclude or limit in any way our liability to you where it would be unlawful to do so. This includes liability for death or personal injury caused by our negligence or the negligence of our employees, agents or subcontractors or for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation.
The Mazoin App is for domestic and private use. If you use the Mazoin App for any commercial, business or resale purpose we will have no liability to you for any loss of profit, loss of business, business interruption, or loss of business opportunity.
We recommend that you back up any content and data used in connection with the Mazoin App, to protect yourself in case of problems with the Mazoin App.
If our provision or support for the Mazoin App is delayed by an event outside our control then we will contact you as soon as possible to let you know and we will take steps to minimise the effect of the delay. Provided we do this we will not be liable for delays caused by the event  but if there is a risk of substantial delay you may contact us to end your contract with us and receive a refund for any Zoins you have paid for but not received.
We May End Your Rights to Use the App If You Break These Terms
We may end your rights to use the Mazoin App at any time by contacting you if you have broken these terms in a serious way. If what you have done can be put right we will give you a reasonable opportunity to do so.
If we end your rights to use the Mazoin App:
you must stop all activities authorised by these terms, including your use of the Mazoin App;
you must delete or remove the Mazoin App from all devices in your possession and immediately destroy all copies of the Mazoin App which you have and confirm to us that you have done this.
</page4>
<page5>
Disputes
We will try to resolve any disputes with you quickly and efficiently.
If you are unhappy with the Mazoin App or our service to you, please contact us as soon as possible. 
If we cannot resolve a dispute using our internal complaint handling procedure, we will:
let you know that we cannot settle the dispute with you; and
give you certain information required by law about alternative dispute resolution; or 
you can chose to bring legal proceedings.
Which laws apply to this Contract
These terms are governed by English and Welsh law and you can bring legal proceedings in the English and Welsh courts. If you live in Scotland you can bring legal proceedings in either the Scottish or the English and Welsh courts. If you live in Northern Ireland you can bring legal proceedings in  either the Northern Irish or the English and Welsh courts. 
Third party rights
No one other than a party to this contract has any right to enforce any term of this contract. 
Deleting your Account
You can delete your Account at any time. You can email us at contact@mazoin.com if you want to delete your Account. When you delete your Account, any Zoins (or any other in app purchases) that you have purchased will no longer be available to you and you will no longer have access to the Mazoin App. Once an Account has been deleted, all data associated with that Account will be deleted and irretrievable. Your Account may take up to 30 days to be permanently closed.
</page5>
</body>
</text>